[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 39, "question": "So you're not exactly on the -- on the breadline, are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", ":", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 40, "answer": "No, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 59, "question": "But do you feel you have?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 60, "answer": "Yes, in many ways.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 69, "question": "When you look back on it, how tough was it, in reality, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "PRP", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 70, "answer": "Well, you know, it -- it depends.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 80, "question": "How did you manage, do you think, to make that break, to get out of that culture?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "TO", "VB", "IN", "JJ", ",", "TO", "VB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 81, "answer": "Well, I had to make the choice personally.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 88, "question": "When that prison door shut for the first time and you were in the cell -- can you remember how you felt?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", ":", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 89, "answer": "Of course.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["California", "New York"]}, "docId": "120113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "RB", "IN", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ":", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "TO", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 95, "question": "Did your behavioral pattern change dramatically when you came out?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "RB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 96, "answer": "It did, but it's also very hard because now you're back into that environment and it's not like all of a sudden I could say -- well, I grew up in this bad place and I don't want to be around these guys anymore, so I'm going to move to California or I'm going to move to New York.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "RBR", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "CC", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 102, "question": "Rough though it was, and tough, what were the things that you got from that lifestyle which have been of benefit to you in the new world that you have?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "CC", "JJ", ",", "WP", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 103, "answer": "Well, that real life experience is so much more powerful, I think, in my job, especially as an actor, than anything, and also in my business approach.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 114, "question": "Are you -- are you a very tough negotiator?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 115, "answer": "I'm not.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 126, "question": "Do the streets ever leave you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "NNS", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 127, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 136, "question": "Is that right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 137, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "WP", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "CC", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "CC", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "CC", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 142, "question": "What does it bring you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 143, "answer": "AHLBERG: A very clear focus on what's important, expressing my gratitude for all the blessings that have been bestowed upon me, and a reminder everyday of what I need to do and what I need to focus on and what I need to stay away from.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "CC", "NN", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "DT", "WDT", "NN", "RP", "TO", "PRP", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "DT", "WDT", "VBP", "VBG", "NNP", "CC", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RP", "TO", "CC", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 144, "question": "When you pray, what do you pray for?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 145, "answer": "I pray to be a good servant to God, a father, a husband, a son, a friend, brother and uncle, a good neighbor, a good leader to those that look up to me and a good follower to those that are serving God and doing the right thing and people that it can look up to and, you know, try to emulate.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 186, "question": "But it's a very -- it is a very raw movie, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 187, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "RB", ":", "IN", "MD", "VB", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "RB", "TO", "VB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "CC", "EX", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", ":", "EX", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 197, "question": "Do you know the answer?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 198, "answer": "You know, I -- I probably -- that would be probably the only reason why I'd ever go back to prison, if I had to do something to protect my family, you know, and there was no other -- there was no other means of doing it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "WDT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 199, "question": "What do you family make of your career path?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 200, "answer": "It all depends on which part of my family.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP$", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "RBR", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "WRB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNS", "VBP", "RP", "TO", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "JJ", "CC", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "CC", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 202, "question": "What are the positive parts and what are the negative?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "WP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 203, "answer": "Well, my kids could care less and they hate it when, you know, people come up to us when we're in public and, you know, and the paparazzi and stuff like that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 219, "question": "But the character was sort of probably had to have one and you did a deal not to have one, but the deal was you would still appear naked on screen, is that right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "RB", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "CD", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "RB", "TO", "VB", "CD", ",", "CC", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 220, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 223, "question": "How did you hear about that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 224, "answer": "Tell me about the deal.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 236, "question": "But a deal worked in to keep your wife happy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 237, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Daniel Day-Lewis", "Russell Crowe"], "LOCATION": ["Denzel Washington"]}, "docId": "120113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ":"], "qSentId": 246, "question": "I mean, who -- who do you really rate out there in the acting world?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "WP", ":", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 247, "answer": "Daniel Day-Lewis, Russell Crowe, Denzel Washington --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "VBP", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 251, "question": "-- and a great actor?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 252, "answer": "-- kind of actors.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 261, "question": "Are you sad \"Entourage\" is over?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "``", "NNP", "''", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 262, "answer": "Very.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 275, "question": "What do you think of the basic shallowness of Hollywood, the fact that if you're a hot star, everyone is crawling all over you, kissing ass, the moment it goes cold, boom?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "DT", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBG", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 276, "answer": "That's why you need people around you that will keep you grounded.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Hollywood"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 281, "question": "Have you got one out there that you think, if I get the chance, that's what I want to do?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "IN", "RB", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "POS", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 282, "answer": "I want to play you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 288, "question": "That kind of lofty ambition?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 289, "answer": "I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 320, "question": "If you're President Obama and you're trying to deal with this obviously huge problem, what do you do about that problem, that part of it, the need to finance a family?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 321, "answer": "Well, it's -- it's extremely difficult.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 334, "question": "You dropped out, then you went to prison and now you're this billion dollar movie star?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RP", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "NN", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 335, "answer": "And I say the odds of you doing that are slim to none.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 373, "question": "How important has your wife been to you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "VBN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 374, "answer": "She's the most important person in my life.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 381, "question": "What's in the pipeline?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 382, "answer": "A lot of different things.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "RB", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "WRB", "NN", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 401, "question": "When you look back over this amazing career you've had, with all the twists and turns, if I had the power to let you relive one moment again, what would you choose?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ",", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "CD", "NN", "RB", ",", "WDT", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 402, "answer": "I would probably choose not quitting school because that's when everything started to go downhill.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBN", "."], "qSentId": 421, "question": "How do you feel?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 422, "answer": "Blessed.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "RB", "RB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 428, "question": "What do you think your dad would have made of the Mark Wahlberg sitting in front of me now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 429, "answer": "You know what, he was around long enough to see me turn it around.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mark Wahlberg"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Prague"]}, "docId": "120113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "NN", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 478, "question": "In a different way, but a similar kind of struggle?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 479, "answer": "One of the things that he said when he first arrived in Prague, he said, remember, I'm not making a civil rights movie right here.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 535, "question": "Is it shocking?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 536, "answer": "No, it's par -- it's par for the course.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 568, "question": "Are you surprised that we're three years after President Barack Obama is elected, and you're still having to have this kind of battle in a place like Hollywood?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 569, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Barack Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJR", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 580, "question": "Do you believe that since Barack Obama was elected, America has become more or less racist?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "VBN", ",", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RBR", "CC", "JJR", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 581, "answer": "I hope -- you know, I'm an optimist, so I think less racist.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Barack Obama"], "LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 599, "question": "How do you think Barack Obama's been doing as president?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 600, "answer": "You know, it's a hard job.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Barack Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 615, "question": "But, my God, how do you deal with all of the pressures coming from every possible place?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", ",", "PRP$", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 616, "answer": "It's almost an impossible job.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 634, "question": "ORGAN: Doesn't the movie that you've made here -- doesn't that absolutely -- and, indeed, the making of this movie, doesn't that show you that you have to have courage?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", ":", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "RB", ":", "CC", ",", "RB", ",", "DT", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 635, "answer": "Right.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", "WP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 636, "question": "You have to have an instinct for taking a big gamble and for pushing against that kind of partisan view, doesn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "CC", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 637, "answer": "Well said what you just said.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 665, "question": "How big is this Tebow thing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 666, "answer": "It's unbelievable.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Tebow"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["NFL"]}, "docId": "120113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "JJS", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 668, "question": "Do you like it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 669, "answer": "I'm not the biggest NFL fan because I'm not American.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 681, "question": "When you do the Tebow, you feel this surging power, don't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 682, "answer": "You feel an energy, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Tebow"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Patrick Reilly"]}, "docId": "120113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", ":", "."], "qSentId": 689, "question": "Tell me about Bowie and you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 690, "answer": "It came from a writer, Patrick Reilly (ph).", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bowie"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 706, "question": "Do you know Bowie?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 707, "answer": "I do know him.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bowie"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", ":", "IN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 712, "question": "You were e-mail buddies with David Bowie?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 713, "answer": "We would just -- for only like a week or something.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["David Bowie"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "VBD", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 728, "question": "And you're email each other saying, what are you watching on TV?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", "VBG", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 729, "answer": "Yeah, then we both put on the same show that each other were watching.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 731, "question": "Do you have his e-mail address?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 732, "answer": "I think I lost it now.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["David Bowie"]}, "docId": "120113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "CD", "NNS", "JJ", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 737, "question": "How cool is David Bowie?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 738, "answer": "I think he's 65 years old, David Bowie.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["David Bowie"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Britain"]}, "docId": "120113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 739, "question": "Is that right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 740, "answer": "Yes, he can finally get a free bus pass in Britain.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 758, "question": "If I can't email Bowie, can I e-mail you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "NNP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 759, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bowie"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 761, "question": "I can't e-mail you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "JJ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 762, "answer": "You can go through my publicist.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 769, "question": "Is he going to kill him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 770, "answer": "He's going to kill it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "RB", "VB", "PRP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 773, "question": "Can you do it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 774, "answer": "I can't even do it, because I don't want to take his impression.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 775, "question": "But if you were doing me, what would you do?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "PRP", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 776, "answer": "I would do his impression.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 777, "question": "What are my weaknesses?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 778, "answer": "It's just great.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "."], "qSentId": 792, "question": "Why would I love that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 793, "answer": "You have to.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120113pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 818, "question": "You are, aren't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 819, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]